boletosexpress.com 2019-04-05

# Privacy Policy - Boletos Express

Boletos Express Inc., via its Boletos Express ticket selling module and in accordance with signed Agency agreements, offers Event Promoters the ability to sell their event tickets on the internet. A necessary component of such a transaction is the exchange of information between a patron and the www.boletosexpress.com website. Various information types are shared, and each has unique privacy considerations outlined below.

## Restrictions

There are No Refunds or Exchanges for any ticket purchased to any event hosted on the Boletos Express website.

## Information Collected from Web Patrons

### Contact information:

While placing online orders at www.boletosexpress.com, you are asked to provide your full name, email address, address, and phone number.

### Order Entry:

Placing orders at www.boletosexpress.com requires the submission of valid credit card information. Specifically, you must provide the name on the credit card, the credit card number, its expiration date and CSC (3 digit security code on the back of your credit card).

### IP Information/Cookies:

For each visitor to the www.boletosexpress.com website, Boletos Express Inc.'s web server automatically recognizes and stores information, such as the visitor's IP address/domain name combination. Additionally, while visiting www.boletosexpress.com, we may use an industry-wide technology called "cookies" which stores certain information on your computer.

## Use of Collected Information

### Personal Information:

As outlined above, some of your personal information is collected as a result of transacting online at www.boletosexpress.com. Personal information is required and offered only to the promoter of the event to which you have purchased tickets. It may be used if that promoter must contact you with regard to the event for which you have purchased tickets or to alert you to his/her future events. Furthermore, all employees of Boletos Express Inc. are bound by the company Client Privacy Policy and are therefore subject to strict guidelines regarding the use of all client information. We keep personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for our business. We also keep information to resolve disputes, enforce our agreements and as otherwise required by law. Personal information will only be disclosed by Boletos Express Inc. to a third party in the event of bankruptcy, or ownership transfer of Boletos Express Inc., or as necessary to comply with the law.

### Financial Information:

The purpose of acquiring your financial information is to authorize payment for purchased goods, and subsequently to bill the appropriate party for said goods. In completing a financial transaction on the www.boletosexpress.com website, you agree to share your financial information with Boletos Express Inc., our service providers, and any banking institutions necessary to complete the transaction. Please note that Boletos Express Inc. stores only the last four digits and expiration date of each credit card number processed through the Boletos Express system. This information can be used by the promoter to confirm that patrons picking up tickets are the same people who placed the online ticket order.

### IP Addresses / Cookies:

IP addresses are collected by Boletos Express Inc. solely in the interest of amassing demographic statistics about its users. We use this information to understand visitor traffic patterns through our website for the purpose of enhancing its usability. Similarly, the use of cookies enables us to customize your experience to better match your interests and preferences, or to simply facilitate your signing in to use the services.

## Security:

Boletos Express uses 128-bit SSL encryption. All of your personal and financial information travels safely over the internet in this encrypted form. Furthermore, all sales data stored on Boletos Express Inc.'s hardware is accessible only to employees, promoters and technicians provided with appropriate security privileges. While Boletos Express Inc. cannot guarantee that unauthorized access to sales and customer data will never occur, we do take great care in protecting your information against loss and misuse.

By completing this registration form, you consent to Boletos Express using and disclosing the information you submit, as described in the preceding paragraphs.

If you are under 13 years old, you must not fill in this form or provide any information about yourself.

As a user of this web site, you agree that you are subject to this web site's Terms of Use as stated in our Privacy Policy at www.boletosexpress.com.

## WEATHER

You bear all risks of inclement weather. This include but not limited to — snow, rain, tornadoes, hurricanes, blizzards, fog, and floods, etc.   
If the event is rescheduled your tickets are valid for the new date and we do not issue refunds..   
If the event takes place and you didn' attend due to weather or for personal choice we do not issue refunds.   
Refunds are only issued if your event is canceled and only the face value of tickets are refunded.   
Its considered an Act of God outside the carrier's control. If the events happen, there are usually hundreds of customers that are affected, as well.   
Event date and time are subject to change, we will do every effort possible to notify you via email or text message.
